

BRANDON MCBRIDE

SENIOR DEVOPS PROFESSIONAL

(276) 274-0305

mcbridebr@gmail.com



ABOUT ME

Senior DevOps Engineer and Solution Architect with proven experience working with cloud solutions, automation, continuous integration/continuous delivery, orchestration, and containerization. Building a career in developing and implementing mission critical solutions while supporting both client and internal development teams.



WORK EXPERIENCE

2011 - Present

CGI Federal

Solution Architect and Product Owner

- Utilize Kubernetes, Openshift, Helm, and Jenkins Pipelines, and Ansible in support of a product offering with millions of lines fo code.
- Coordinate work between multiple devops engineering teams supporting multiple solution groups and cilent teams on recurring quarterly product implementation cycles while operating in an agile setting with two week sprints.
- Develop new automation for application build and deployment efforts across more than fourty environments both in the cloud and on premise.
- Fill the role of Mentor and Leader for more than thirty members in a fast pace environment.

2010 - 2011

Scientific Research Corporation

Quality Analyst II

- Perform quality assurance testing on communications software developed for the United States Space and Naval Warfare Systems Center.
- Work with a team of engineers to ensure mission critical software patches and updates are securely delivered to military assets around the world.

2008 - 2010

CGI

Test Analyst

- Drive testing on critical software and applications in support of one of the nations top telecom companies.
- Write complex manual test cases for highly integrated hosted software.
- Track critical defects to resolution.



TECH STACK

Jenkins Pipelines

Kubernetes

Helm

OpenShift

Ansible

Linux

Azure

AWS



SOFT SKILLS

Leadership

Project Management

DevOps

Architecture



EDUCATION

B.S. in Computer Information Systems

Appalachian State University 2005 - 2007

A.S. Business Administration

Wilkes Community College 2003 - 2005



CERTIFICATIONS

Security +

CompTIA

2010 - Present